KATHY TRUJILLO

Denver, CO 80219

Phone: (305)215-1231 | Email: kati.k220@gmail.com
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kathy-trujillo-498061158

GitHub: https://github.com/trukat | Portfolio: https://trukat.github.io/my_portfolio/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Fintech and small-business lending industry. This experience has provided me with ample problem-solving skills and coming up with creative solutions on how to tackle new challenges. I look forward to applying these capabilities to developing effective & user-friendly applications.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, CSS, HTML5, Node.js, Bootstrap, Web APIs, JQuery, Materialize, NodeJS, Express and MySQL

PROJECTS

Villagers 101 | https://github.com/trukat/Villagers_101 | https://radiant-woodland-55913.herokuapp.com/

- This application was built collaboratively and solves real-world problems by integrating data received from using the MVC paradigm and server-side API. The hope of this web application is to provide a fun and interactive search engine tool that is simple to navigate.
- Materialize is the CSS framework used to style the web page, Animal Crossing API is for the search application, and NPM for Node JavaScript platform.
- Built with: animal-crossing npm, express, express-session npm, passport, passport-local npm, bcryptjs npm, mysql2 npm, dotenv npm, sequelize npm, sequelize cli, VSCode, MySQL Workbench

Travel Almanac | https://github.com/trukat/Travel_Almanac | https://jtwob.github.io/Travel_Almanac/

- This project combines country & weather data to create a travel almanac, presenting
 users with key information related to the country of their choice, as well as an interactive
 map & a 5-day forecast for their destination point.
- First team project, collaborated on research & development
- Built with: HTML, CSS, Materialize, Font Awesome, JQuery, Javascript. REST Countries v1 API, OpenWeather API & OpenLayers API

Eat-Da-Burger | https://github.com/trukat/burger_app | https://eat-da-burger-hndlbrs.herokuapp.com/

- Eat-Da-Burger! is a restaurant app that lets users input the names of burgers they'd like to eat
- Whenever a user submits a burger's name, your app will display the burger on the left side of the page -- waiting to be devoured. Each burger in the waiting area also has a 'Devoured' button. When the user clicks it, the burger will move to the right side of the page
- Built with: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Font Awesome, jQuery, mySQL, Express, Express-handlebars, Javascript

EXPERIENCE

OnDeck Capital, Inc., Denver, CO

Risk Administration & Vendor Management Lead

January 2019 – Present

- Promoted within company because of demonstrated leadership skills
- Supervise and report on the performance of 2 third-party collection agencies to ensure delivery in line with contractual obligations, compliance and overall strategy
- Conduct third party audits and complete onboarding of third-party vendors
- Demonstrate ability to build and leverage strong relationships and networks both within and outside the organization
- Solid track record of identifying and capturing sustainable, hard savings

Customer Service Operations Support

April 2018 – December 2018

- Production environment focused around meeting deadlines input payments & remittances into Calico/Salesforce systems while following standard operating procedures and customer specific instructions for processing
- Collaborate daily with several teams including customer service, payment support, sales, finance, legal and tech ops to ensure consistency

Operations Support Administrator

August 2017 – April 2018

- Performed risk assessment: analyzed current risks and identified potential accounts following key indicators to be sold to litigation firms
- Maximized procedural efficiency, enhancing the work flow of related departments
- Manage difficult situations with customers and provided them with a resolution, information or additional options; ensured a quick and proper response to all reasonable customer requests

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

UC Berkeley Extension, Berkeley, CA

September 2020-Present

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS

Bachelor of Arts in Criminal Justice

Florida International University, Miami, FL

August 2009- December 2012